Mss.B.Sh35
American Philosophical Society
- Correspondence
  - Letter to [William Sharswood], Nov. 29, 1867; 8-3/4x5-1/2; Munich. Bayerische Staatsbibliothek
    L.S.: Lipowsky. 1p. In German. (see W. Sharswood. Letters ...; 1865-1867.) ----Copy. Thanks for his publication.
  - Letter to W[illiam] Sharswood, March 28; 5-1/4x3-1/2; Morris, M. H.
    A.L.S. 2p. (see W.Shars wood. Letters...; 1865-1867.) Concerning Charles T. Jackson.
  - Letter to [William] Sharswood, Oct. 10; 7x4-1/2; Lander, Mrs.
    Philadelphia, A.L.in 3rd.P. 1p. (see W. Sharswood. Letters...; 1865-1867.) Concerning his publication.
  - Letter to [William] Sharswood, undated; 5-1/2x3-1/2; Allen, George, 1808-1876
    Sunday morning. A.L.S. 2p. (see W.Sharswood. Letters...; 1865-1867.) Will not introduce him to a priest.
  - Letter to [William] Sharswood, undated; 5-1/2x3-1/2; Allen, George, 1808-1876
    Sunday evening. A.L.S.with initials. 1p. (see W.Sharswood. Letters...; 1865-1867.) Will send his carte-de-visite when they are printed.
  - Letter to [William] Sharswood, undated; 5-1/2x3-1/2; Allen, George, 1808-1876
    Monday evening. A.L.S. 1p. (see W.Sharswood. Letters...; 1865-1867.) Will leave the volume with the maid so that he can get it when he wishes.
  - Letter to [William] Sharswood, undated; 5-1/2x3-1/2; Allen, George, 1808-1876
    Tuesday morning. A.L.S. 1p. (see W. Sharswood. Letters...; 1865-1867.) Concerning publications.
  - Letter to [William] Sharswood, undated; Allen, George, 1808-1876
    Saturday PM. A.L.S.
  - Letter to [William Sharswood]., undated; 8x5; Burton(?), J. G.
    L. 1p. (see W.Sharswood. Letters...; 1865-1867.) Cannot comply with his request.
  - Letter to William P.[sic] Sharswood, undated; 8x5-1/4; Corson, Hiram, 1828-1911
    Annapolis. A.L.S. 1p. (see W.Sharswood Letters...; 1865-1867.) Has been ill and will not arrive in Philadelphia for another week.
  - Letter to [William] Sharswood, undated; 8x5; Hosmer, Jean, 1842-1890
    Tuesday morning. A.L.S. 1p. (see W.Sharswood. Letters...; 1765-1867.) Cannot be with him as planned.
  - Letter to W[illiam] Sharswood, undated; 7-1/2x5; Hosmer, Jean, 1842-1890
    Tuesday, A.M. A.L.S. 1p. (see W.Sharswood Letters...; 1865-1867.) Thanks for his gift.
  - Letter to W[illiam] Sharswood., undated; 7-1/2x5; Hosmer, Jean, 1842-1890
    A.L.in 3rd.P. 1p.and add. (see W.Sharswood. Letters...; 1865-1867.) Cannot be with him this afternoon.
  - Letter to [William Sharswood], undated; 7x4-1/2; Pearce, James
    Monday. A.L.S. 1p. (see W.Sharswood Letters...; 1865-1867.) Has returned the borrowed play.